[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question" : "The next.js is based upon ?",
        "options": [
            "JavaScript",
            "Python",
            "React",
            "Java"
        ],
        "answer": "React"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question" : "Next.js used for ?",
        "options": [
            "Server side",
            "Client side"
        ],
        "answer": "Server side"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question" : "Is next.js an open-soure framework?",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question" : "Is Next.js a frontend framework or a backend framework?",
        "options": [
            "Backend",
            "Frontend",
            "Both"
        ],
        "answer": "Frontend"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question" : "Next.js is written in which of the following language?",
        "options": [
            "JavaScript",
            "TypeScript",
            "Rust",
            "All of the above",
            "Only B and C",
            "Only A and C"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question" : "Who developed Next.js?",
        "options": [
            "Tim Berners-Lee",
            "Guillermo Rauch",
            "Brendan Eich"
        ],
        "answer": "Guillermo Rauch"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question" : "In Next.js, we can quickly edit the top section of each react page by using the built-in --- react component?",
        "options": [
            "Metadata",
            "Head",
            "Top"
        ],
        "answer": "Head"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question" : "In Next.js, what is the name of the Inbuild CSS-in-js library?",
        "options": [
            "Style.js",
            "Style.css",
            "Style-jsx"
        ],
        "answer": "Style-jsx"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question" : "How many types of pre-rendering are supported by Next.js?",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
        ],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question" : "Which of the following pre-rendering method generates the HTML page at build time?",
        "options": [
            "Static Generation",
            "Server-side generation"
        ],
        "answer": "Static Generation"
    }
]